# João Devson Mucavel

Software Developer





## **EXPERIENCE**

ITGest Moçambique | Developer | 2019 - 2024

Developed and Implemented two Software Products at **Banco de Mocambique**:

- BM Eventos: Event Management Solution.
- **ID4Service**: Service Desk Platform.

Developed a Solution to automate the Clearing and Settlement process of Card Transactions at ATMs and POSs - **BSeC**, for **Standard Bank**.

Participated in the development of the Account Opening Workflow and Payment Method onboarding for *Moza Banco*.

Developed interactive technological solutions for Queue Management and Spaces.

**Brand Lovers** | Web Developer | 2018 – 2019 Developed Websites and Web-based Systems.

Self-Employed | Developer | 2017 – 2018

Developed AI and AR / VR solutions.

Cloud Digital Arts | Web Developer | 2015 - 2017

Developed Interactive and Innovative Solutions for Small and Medium-sized companies.

Developed Websites and Web and Mobile-based Systems..



### **TRAINING**

Systems and Networks Administration  $\mid$  USTM  $\mid$  2016 - 2017(?)

Degree in Information Systems and Network Administration, at Universidade São Tomás de Moçambique. (interrupted).

Computer Systems Programming | IICAEG | 2011 – 2013 The course covers essential computing and systems development concepts, focusing on emerging technologies in the job market. Having the privilege of concluding with a score of 14.



### **HOBBY**

A good reading session, especially on topics related to technology.



## **ABOUT ME**

Graduated in Computer Systems Programming from the Instituto Industrial e de Computação Armando Emílio Guebuza. He has solid experience in several programming languages, systems analysis and software development, having participated in relevant projects, such as the implementation of solutions at Banco de Moçambique. He is highly skilled at solving problems, working in a team and managing time effectively.



## **SKILLS**

Web Development

Mobile (Android & iOS)

Desktop

Networking



### **PERSONALITY**

Proactive

Adaptable

Communicative

Resilient



#### **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese

**English** 

Changana

Japanese (A special fondness for this

language)



Online resumé - https://shorturl.at/9xRR1



(+258) 844559091



ivel

